Wolff, Sidney A. Arbitration Files 5131
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
- Westinghouse Electric - Zylite Optical Company PLUS MISCELLANEOUS. (Box 34)
  - White Plains Iron Works -and- Local 455, Shopmen's Union, 1966 (Box 34, Folder 6)
  - Wilcox + Gibbs Local 72, Ind. Union of Marine's Shipbuilding Workers, 1957 (Box 34, Folder 7)
  - Winard, Inc. with Local 1 - International Jewelry Workers Union, 1948 (Box 34, Folder 8)
  - Wodham Corporation with American Communications Association, CIO, 1949 (Box 34, Folder 9)
  - Wood Container Co. - Local 3147 - Furniture + Wood Novelty Workers - Mediation Board, 1947 (Box 34, Folder 10)
  - Wolta Electrical Products Corp. with Local 475 UERMWA, 1948 (Box 34, Folder 11)
  - Woolen Jobbers Association Local 65, 1961 (Box 34, Folder 12)
  - Yale Club - Local 6 - Hotel + Club Employees Union, 1961 (Box 34, Folder 13)
  - Yorkshire 514, 1961 (Box 34, Folder 14)
  - Zylite Optical Company, Inc. with Wholesale and Warehouse Workers Union, Local 65, 1950 (Box 34, Folder 15)
  - E.W. Bliss Company - District 27, Local 4396, USA, 1968 (Box 34, Folder 16)
  - Chrysler New York Company, -and- United Automobile Workers, CIO, Local 259, 1955 (Box 34, Folder 17)
  - The New Wage and Hour Law, 1949 (Box 34, Folder 18)
  - The Social Security Almanac, 1946-1947 (Box 34, Folder 19)
  - Grandview Dairy, Inc. -and- Milk Wagon Drivers Union, Local 584, 1939 (Box 34, Folder 20)
  - 'The New Labor Law' What the Labor-Management Relations Act means to- Businessmen, Workers, Unions and their Advisors, 1947 (Box 34, Folder 21)
  - The Portal-To-Portal Act of 1947 (Box 34, Folder 22)
  - Hourly Unit Agreement - Sperry Gyroscope Company -and- I.U.E.R.M.W., CIO Local 450, 1955-1957 (Box 34, Folder 23)
  - Standard Dry Cargo and Passenger Ship Agreement - The Radio Officers' Union, 1951-1952 (Box 34, Folder 24)
  - Standard Dry Cargo and Passenger Ship Agreement - The Radio Officers' Union, 1954 (Box 34, Folder 25)
  - The Singer Manufacturing Company, 1947 (Box 34, Folder 26)
  - Service Parts Department Shop Agreement Local No. 229 I.U.U.A.A.A.I.W.A., 1950 (Box 34, Folder 27)
  - American Woolen Company -an-d Textile Workers Union of America, CIO, 1952 (Box 34, Folder 28)
  - Celanese Corporation of America -and- Celanese Local 1874, 1950 (Box 34, Folder 29)
  - Celanese Corporation of America -and- United Construction Workers (Local 153), 1954 (Box 34, Folder 30)
  - Celanese Construction Workers (Local 153) U.M.W.A., 1951 (Box 34, Folder 31)
  - American Machine and Foundry Company UAW-CIO, 1949-1950 (Box 34, Folder 32)
  - Celanese Corporation of America Local 1874, 1948 (Box 34, Folder 33)
  - Celanese Corporation of America -and- Celanese Local 1874, 1947 (Box 34, Folder 34)
  - Celanese Corporation of America -and- United Construction Workers Local 153, 1945-1946 (Box 34, Folder 35)
  - The Singer Manufacturing Company - Agreement, 1949 (Box 34, Folder 36)
  - Brewers, Bottlers, Drivers, Chauffeurs, Drivers and Chauffeurs, Helpers, Stablemen and Yardmen, 1945 (Box 34, Folder 37)
  - Celanese Corporation of America -and- Celanese Local 1874 T.W.U.A., 1942-1945 (Box 34, Folder 38)
  - Mack Manufacturing Corporation -and- I.U.U.A.A.A.I.W.A. Local 229, 1950 (Box 34, Folder 39)
  - The Prudential Insurance Company of America -and- Insurance Agents' International Union (AFL), 1952 (Box 34, Folder 40)
  - Liberty Products Corporation -and- Liberty Lodge No. 1767 of the I.A.M., 1954 (Box 34, Folder 41)
  - Mack Manufacturing Corporation -and- I.U.U.A.A.A.I.W.A. Local No. 677, 1950 (Box 34, Folder 42)
  - Amalgamated Lithographers of America Local 1, 1947 (Box 34, Folder 43)
  - San Francisco Retailers' Council -and- Department Store Employees' Union, 1949 (Box 34, Folder 44)
  - Royal Typewriter Co., Inc. -and- Local 265 UERMWA, 1947 (Box 34, Folder 45)
  - The Singer Manufacturing Company - Agreement, 1951 (Box 34, Folder 46)
  - Simplicity Pattern Co., Inc. -and- Local 16, United Office and Professional Workers of America, CIO, 1946-1947 (Box 34, Folder 47)
  - Railway Express Agency, Inc. -and- I.B.T. Locals 459, 808, 1954 (Box 34, Folder 48)
  - New York Post -and- Newspaper Guild of New York, 1949-1950 (Box 34, Folder 49)
  - Lodge 402 of District 15 I.A.M. and Nathan Manufacturing Company, 1948 (Box 34, Folder 50)
  - United Telephone Organizations and the New York Telephone company, 1950-1951 (Box 34, Folder 51)
  - Telephone Workers Union of New Jersey -and- New Jersey Bell Telephone Company, 1953 (Box 34, Folder 52)
  - Precision Castings Company, Inc. Fayetteville, N.Y. - Agreement, 1953 (Box 34, Folder 53)
  - Republic Steel Corporation -and- I.A.M. Lodge 402 District 15, 1947 (Box 34, Folder 54)
  - U.E.R.M.W.A. Local 407 -and- U.S. Tool Company, Inc. (Box 34, Folder 55)
  - Paint Varnish and Allied Products Local 1310 -and- Sherwin-Williams Co., 1954 (Box 34, Folder 56)
  - American Chain and Cable Company, Inc.-and- Local no. 4818 U.S.W.A., CIO, 1954 (Box 34, Folder 57)
  - Celanese Corporation of America -and- United Construction Workers U.M.W.A., 1954 (Box 34, Folder 58)
  - Marinette Paper Company -and- U.M.W.A. Dist. 50 Local 13275, 1955 (Box 34, Folder 59)
  - E.I. Du Pont De Nemours and Company -and- Chemical Workers Association, Inc., 1953 (Box 34, Folder 60)
  - Fairchild Engine and Airplane Corporation -and- Local 661 I.U.U.A.A.A.I.W.A. (UAW-CIO), 1953 (Box 34, Folder 61)
  - Fairchild Engine and Airplane Corporation -and- Local 661 I.U.U.A.A.A.I.W.A., 1953 (Box 34, Folder 62)
  - Hampton Looms of Virginia, Inc. -and- Textile Workers Union of America (CIO), 1952 (Box 34, Folder 63)
  - Industrial Rayon Corporation (Covington, Virginia Plant) -and- Local 202 T.W.U.A. CIO, 1953 (Box 34, Folder 64)
  - Industrial Rayon Corporation -and- Local 482 T.W.U.A. CIO, 1953 (Box 34, Folder 65)
  - Local 306, 1951 (Box 34, Folder 66)
  - Machinery Co., Inc. -and- I.A.M., AFL-CIO (Box 34, Folder 67)
  - Local 575 United Gas, Coke and Chemical Workers of America -and- Merck and Co., Inc., 1954 (Box 34, Folder 68)
  - General Foods Corporation -and- Amalgamated Food and Allied workers Union Local 56, 1953 (Box 34, Folder 69)
  - Motion Picture Industry in New York -and- Screen Office Professional Employees Guild, Local 109, 1946 (Box 34, Folder 70)
  - Midtown Realty Owners' Association, Inc. -and- Local 164, 1948-1951 (Box 34, Folder 71)
  - Mutual Chemical Company of America -and- Local 191, United Gas, Coke and Chemical Workers of America, 1949 (Box 34, Folder 72)
  - McKiernan-Terry Corporation -and- Lodge 1867 I.A.M., 1952 (Box 34, Folder 73)
  - Celanese Corporation of America -and- Celanese Local 1874 T.W.U.A., 1948 (Box 34, Folder 74)
  - Greater N.Y. Photo Finishers Association, Inc. -and- United Photographic Employees Union Local No. 415 CIO, 1945-1947 (Box 34, Folder 75)
  - Directory of Affiliates and Constitution of the AFL, 1949 (Box 34, Folder 76)
  - Paper Machinery Co., Inc. -and- District 15 of the I.A.M., AFL (Box 34, Folder 77)
  - Realty Advisory Board on Labor Relations (Incorporated) -and- Local 32B Building Service Employees International Union, AFL, 1950-1951 (Box 34, Folder 78)
  - Royal Typewriter Co., Inc. -and- Local 265 U.E.R.M.W.A. CIO, 1946 (Box 34, Folder 79)
  - Federal Union No. 21754 -and- Culinary Workers Local Union No. 623, 1952 (Box 34, Folder 80)
  - Constitution of I.B.T. Chauffeurs, Warehousemen and Helpers of America, 1940 (Box 34, Folder 81)
  - Celanese Corporation of America -and- Textile Workers Union of America CIO, 1950 (Box 34, Folder 82)
  - Celanese Corporation of America -and- Celanese Local 1874 T.W.U.A., 1950 (Box 34, Folder 83)
  - The Bassick Company -and- Basic Local No. 229 I.U.E.R.M.W. (CIO), 1954 (Box 34, Folder 84)
  - American Can Company -and- U.S.W.A. CIO, 1954 (Box 34, Folder 85)
  - American Enka Corporation and the Textile Workers Union of America CIO Local No. 1054, 1949 (Box 34, Folder 86)
  - Local 404, U.E.R.M.W.A., CIO -and- Anaconda Wire and Cable Company (Box 34, Folder 87)
  - American Newspaper Guild -and- United Press Association, 1955-1957 (Box 34, Folder 88)
  - The American Steel and Wire Company of New Jersey and the United Steelworkers of America CIO, 1947 (Box 34, Folder 89)
  - Celanese Corporation of America -and- Celanese Local 1874 T.W.U.A CIO, 1948 (Box 34, Folder 90)
  - Celanese Corporation of America -and- Celanese Local 1874 T.W.U.A. CIO, 1950 (Box 34, Folder 91)
  - Celanese Corporation of America -and- T.W.U.A., 1950 (Box 34, Folder 92)
  - Celanese Corporation of America -and- T.W.U.A., 1951 (Box 34, Folder 93)
  - Celanese Corporation of America -and- T.W.U.A., 1952 (Box 34, Folder 94)
  - Celanese Corporation of America -and- T.W.U.A., 1953 (Box 34, Folder 95)
  - The Bassick Company -and- Local 229 I.U.E.R.M.W. (CIO), 1953 (Box 34, Folder 96)
  - Bridgeport-Lycoming -and- UAW-CIO, 1953 (Box 34, Folder 97)
  - Celanese Corporation of America -and- United Mine Workers of America, 1954 (Box 34, Folder 98)
  - Celanese Corporation of America -and- United Mine Workers of America, 1954 (Box 34, Folder 99)
  - U.S. Rubber Company -and- T.W.U.A., CIO, 1948 (Box 34, Folder 100)
  - The New York New Haven and Hartford Railroad Co., 1952 (Box 34, Folder 101)
  - The New York New Haven and Hartford Railroad Co., 1952 (Box 34, Folder 102)
  - Boston and Maine Railroad "Minute Man Service", 1952 (Box 34, Folder 103)
  - Local Union No. 42 United Brewery and Soft Drink Workers -and- Standard Brands, Inc. (Box 34, Folder 104)
  - Columbia Pictures Corp. -and- United Office and Professional Workers of America CIO, 1946 (Box 34, Folder 105)
  - Telephone Workers Union of New Jersey -and- New Jersey Bell Company, 1952 (Box 34, Folder 106)
  - Maxwell House Division -and- Meat and Cannery Workers Union Local 56, 1949 (Box 34, Folder 107)
  - Emerson Radio and Phonograph Corporation -and- International Union of Electrical, Radio and Machine Workers CIO (Box 34, Folder 108)
  - Ice Cream Drivers -and- I.B.T. A.F.L., 1957 (Box 34, Folder 109)
  - Westinghouse Electric -Local 401- IERMW, 1958 (Box 34, Folder 110)
  - Westinghouse Electric -Local 617- IERMW, 1958 (Box 34, Folder 111)
  - Westinghouse Electric Corp. - Westinghouse Conf. Bd., I.U.E., 1967 (Box 34, Folder 112)
  - Westinghouse Electric Local 746, 1966 (Box 34, Folder 113)
  - Westinghouse Electric Corp. - National Westinghouse Conference Bd., 1967 (Box 34, Folder 114)
  - Westinghouse Electric -Local 617- IERMW, 1959 (Box 34, Folder 115)
  - White Plains Iron Works -and- Local 455, Shopmen's Union, 1966 (Box 34, Folder 116)
  - Willcox + Gibbs - Local 72, Ind. Union of Marine + Ship Building workers, 1957 (Box 34, Folder 117)
  - Winard, Inc. w. Local 1. International Jewelry Workers Union, 1948 (Box 34, Folder 118)
  - Wodham Corporation with American Communications Association, CIO, 1950 (Box 34, Folder 119)
  - Wood Container Co. Local 3147 - Furniture + Wood Novelty Workers, 1947 (Box 34, Folder 120)
  - Wilts Electrical Products Corp. with Local 475 UERMWA, 1948 (Box 34, Folder 121)
  - Woolen Jobbers Association (Samson Woolen Company) Local 65, 1947 (Box 34, Folder 122)
  - Yale club- Local 6 - Hotel + Club Employees Union, 1961 (Box 34, Folder 123)
  - 514 Forkshire, 1961 (Box 34, Folder 124)
  - Zylite Optical Company, Inc. with Wholesale and Warehouse Workers Union, Local 65, 1950 (Box 34, Folder 125)
  - E.W. Bliss Company - District 27, Local 4396. USA, 1958 (Box 34, Folder 126)
  - S. Wolff Personal, 1959 (Box 34, Folder 127)
  - Subway Committee, 1946-1948 (Box 34, Folder 128)
  - 'Achievement of the Forty-Hour-Week in American History- (Box 34, Folder 129)
  - 'Achievement of the Forty-Hour-Week in American History- (Box 34, Folder 129)